<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Angelic Layer (J)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Kidou Tenshi Angelic Layer - Misaki To Yume No Tenshi-tachi</name>
		<desc>Despite Misaki Suzuhara's short appearance, she is a seventh-grader who just moved to Tokyo to live with her aunt, Shouko Asami. After arriving in the city outside of Tokyo Station, Misaki watches a battle between two dolls on a big live-screen called Angelic Layer, a highly popular game in which players (called Deus) buy and custom-design dolls known as Angels that are moved by mental control when on a field called the "layer." Interested in learning about Angelic Layer, an eccentric man calling himself Icchan, encourages Misaki to purchase and create her own angel. She wants the angel to be "a short girl, but strong and happy", and names it Hikaru. Even though she's clueless about the game, Misaki soon competes in tournaments and is assisted by Icchan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Angelic Layer (J)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011221T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Epoch Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boktai - The Sun is in Your Hand (U)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Boktai: The Sun Is in Your Hand</name>
		<desc>Boktai: The Sun Is in Your Hand is the first Game Boy Advance game that uses sunlight to influence gameplay. In the game, you'll follow the adventures of Django, a young vampire hunter on a quest to rid the world of evil. As Django, you must overcome traps, defeat enemies, and fight through the deepest parts of dungeons. Watch out for the amount of sunlight--Django is stronger by day, while the vampires are stronger by night. The game features a solar sensor on the cartridge and a real-time clock system.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Boktai - The Sun is in Your Hand (U)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boktai 2 - Solar Boy Django (U)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<name>Boktai 2: Solar Boy Django</name>
		<desc>Boktai 2 continues the adventures of Django the Solar Boy as he sets out to rid the world of evil vampires and demons. The second installment in the franchise brings back the solar sensor technology, which incorporates natural sunlight into gameplay. Take advantage of natural sunlight through the built-in solar sensor on the Game Boy Advance cartridge to power up and fuse more than 60 weapons and items. Now you can head outdoors and battle enemies with more weapons, new characters, and a larger game environment.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Boktai 2 - Solar Boy Django (U)(Rising Sun)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20041019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire</name>
		<desc>Long ago in the days of darkness and magic, a young wanderer comes face to face with his destiny. You control the fate of Ryu, a young warrior and descendant of the Light Dragon Clan. Together, with your mystical friend, Nina, you must search for magic spells and mysterious secrets. Along the way, gain experience and skill as you battle against strange monsters. Uncover valuable secrets that will help you on your adventure and unlock the secrets of the Dragon Clan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Breath of Fire (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire 2 (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire II</name>
		<desc>One of the most popular RPGs of all time continues in this epic quest. Enter the magical life of a hero Ryu, a dragon morphing warrior, as he embarks on a vast adventure in search of his missing father and little sister. Eight mysterious characters will join you along the way to help you find and master the hidden secrets of the amazing lands you will explore. Discover the right combinations of magical spells, strength, wisdom, guts, and luck to determine your fate as you master the world of dragons, demons, and mystery.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Breath of Fire 2 (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - 2 in 1 Double Pack (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania Double Pack</name>
		<desc>CASTLEVANIA DOUBLE PACK collects two great Castlevania titles for the Game Boy Advance. The set provides twice the incredible gothic adventure for one low price! In Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance, you'll use your new "Spell Fusion" powers to acquire the relics of Dracula, left behind from 50 years in the past, to unravel the disappearance of your friend Lydie. In Castlevania: Aria Of Sorrow, you'll take on murderous monsters and absorb their souls to gain their abilities--and uncover a terrible secret.

CASTLEVANIA: HARMONY OF DISSONANCE
Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance for GameBoy Advance brings players back into the world of Dracula, a place where unspeakable monsters lurk and powerful magic rules. Only 50 years have passed since Simon Belmont liberated the land from the menacing curse of Dracula. Now Juste Belmont--the latest scion in the legendary family of Vampire hunters--must take up his whip and storm a mysterious castle in search of his childhood friend Lydie.

CASTLEVANIA: ARIA OF SORROW
Its the most exciting Castlevania adventure yet! The year is 2035 and Soma Cruz is about to witness the first solar eclipse of the 21st century when he suddenly blacks out--only to awaken inside a mysterious castle. As Soma, you must navigate the castles labyrinths while confronting perilous monsters at every turn. But beware, you must escape before evil consumes you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - 2 in 1 Double Pack (U)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Circle of the Moon (U)(Cezar).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Circle of the Moon</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has been resurrected and evil will reign supreme unless he is stopped. As Nathan Graves, you'll hunt down the count and use your whip and a variety of special items to destroy his minions. Battle your way through Dracula's castle and rid the world of evil once and for all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Circle of the Moon (U)(Cezar)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Kobe</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance</name>
		<desc>Nearly fifty years has past since Simon Belmont rescued the land from the curse of Dracula. Now, Simon's descendant Juste Belmont, must acquire the relics of Dracula to unravel the disappearance of his childhood friend Lydie. The castle's enchanting mysteries and danger await all those who dare enter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance (U)(Independent)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20020916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Tokyo</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chobits (J)(MUGS).zip</path>
		<name>Chobits for Gameboy Advance: Atashi Dake no Hito</name>
		<desc>Chobits: Atashi Dake no Hito is a GBA game featuring the characters from the anime / manga Chobits.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Chobits (J)(MUGS)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CIMA The Enemy (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>CIMA: The Enemy</name>
		<desc>For decades, the human race and the CIMA race have been in constant conflict with one another. As Ark J, your mission is to guard the gate between the two worlds, protect your appointed town, and ultimately, find peace. You'll progress through a nonlinear storyline while solving puzzles, exploring worlds, and battling enemies. The game includes a combat system that features both action and strategy elements. Another feature lets you activate non-playable characters to help you accomplish your goals.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/CIMA The Enemy (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Custom Robo GX (J)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Custom Robo GX</name>
		<desc>The Game Boy Advance iteration in the Custom Robo franchise.

Custom Robo GX is a Japan-exclusive GBA version of Custom Robo. It maintains the series' trademark RPG-hybrid gameplay, but changes the battle system to accommodate the limited capacity of the GBA.

The Robos can still be customized in the same manner as the console games (Body, Gun, Bomb, Pod, Feet) but the battles take place on a 2-d plane in zero gravity. There is still auto-aim, and the Robos have the same fire modes as the console releases. Different arenas have obstacles, and Robos have dash moves to move around them more effectively. Generally a Robo is based on its 3d counterpart, so a slow and powerful Robo will still be slow and powerful.

This game was originally planned to be the first Custom Robo game released in America, but Nintendo chose the Gamecube release instead.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Custom Robo GX (J)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Doom</name>
		<desc>From the legendary game developers at id Software, comes an explosive journey into the nightmare world of DOOM™. Embark on a harrowing mission to rid of Martian Moon Base of hordes of demonic creatures. Navigate through DOOM™'s 24 maze like levels, scouring the corridors for secret areas and combat aids as you take on hell spawned demons with an explosive arsenal of chainguns, plasma rifles and rocket launchers. Use the Game Boy® Advance Game Link® Cable to team up with a friend and blast the levels together or link up to 4 players for the ultimate deathmatch.®</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Doom (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David A. Palmer Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom II (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Doom II</name>
		<desc>Hell's fury has been unleashed. Billions are dead. To save humanity from certain extinction, you'll have to battle the most powerful demon scum to ever walk the Earth...alone. Blast your way through id Software's original mind-blowing, adrenaline-pumping, record-breaking sequel. It's your bloodiest demon slaughter yet. Now in an explosive handheld version!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Doom II (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics Advance (U)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics Advance</name>
		<desc>When Marche and his friends open an ancient magical tome, their small town is transformed into a fantasy-filled kingdom known as Ivalice. Now, Marche must take up the sword and master the arts of war if he has any hope of returning home. Guide Marche and his clan against countless foes in tactical combat and discover the wonders of Ivalice. How will you restore your town to normal...and do you even want to?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fantasy Tactics Advance (U)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem</name>
		<desc>The rightful heir to the throne of Rikea is finally returning home after many years lost to her people. But before the celebrations can begin, you must first guard her through the evil lands that await before you, by taking charge of an elite group of soldiers possessing skills unlike any other.

The first Fire Emblem title to be released outside of Japan includes an all new quest featuring a selection of warriors, wizards and dragons (both good and bad). Battle through turn-based environments and choose your moves wisely, as those you lose during a fight will be lost for good.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Fire Emblem (U)(Venom)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - The Sacred Stones (U)(TrashMan).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: The Sacred Stones</name>
		<desc>In Fire Emblem: The Sacred Stones, you must help protect the nation of Renais from the invading Grado Empire. Plan your strategy, choose your units, and then lead your soldiers in to battle. The more experience your soldiers gain, the more you can upgrade their abilities. This time, your soldiers can gain experience by fighting new monsters in the Tower of Valni.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Fire Emblem - The Sacred Stones (U)(TrashMan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost Trap (J)(Cezar).zip</path>
		<name>Ghost Trap</name>
		<desc>Ghost Trap is an Action Adventure game, developed by Artoon and published by Eidos Interactive, which was released in Japan in 2002.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ghost Trap (J)(Cezar)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goemon New Age Shutsudou! (J)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Goemon: New Age Shutsudou!</name>
		<desc>Goemon: New Age Shutsudou! gives the franchise a facelift, putting Goemon and his friends in a futuristic rendition of Japan, fending off a supernatural force threatening the city.

Goemon: New Age Shutsudou! is a Japan only title in the Ganbare Goemon franchise. New Age Shutsudou is a semi-port/remake of Ganbare Goemon: Shin Sedai Shuumei, containing similar levels and plot to the PlayStation title. New Age Shutsudou was developed and published by Konami Corporation in 2002. The game (as well as Shin Sedai Shuumei) gives the Goemon universe a facelift. It takes place in futuristic Japan, Goemon is skinnier and sports a new hair-do, Ebisumaru is replaced with a shy girl who has a crush on Goemon named Ebisu, and Yae is replaced with Yui, a mermaid-like creature. 

 The Impact scenes take place inside of a large mech.
In terms of gameplay, Goemon: New Age Shutsudou! is a fairly traditional side-scrolling action platformer. The player controls either Goemon or Ebisu, attacking enemies with their respective weapons (which can be leveled up three times in terms of power), and gathering coins. Each level is fairly linear in comparison to earlier Ganbare Goemon titles, and at the end of each level the player is taken to a world map. 

Some levels differentiate from this formula. These levels put the player in control of different characters. There are side-scrolling shoot-em-up stages starring characters like Sasuke. The weapon power-up system still works identically here, the gameplay style is just shifted. Additionally, there are stages where the player takes control of Yui, a mermaid-like creature. These stages are underwater. 

New Age Shutsudou marks the return of the first person Impact scenes, which were previously in some of the Super Famicom Goemon games. These scenes put the player in control of a large mech, fighting other robots. The mech is immobile, but is able to melee attack, guard, and fire counter-attacking lasers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Goemon New Age Shutsudou! (J)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun</name>
		<desc>Golden Sun is the first original role-playing game for the Game Boy Advance to appear in the U.S. And despite perhaps a too-familiar storyline, Golden Sun's jaw-dropping graphics, deep magic system, and unique multiplayer arena mode truly show that the Game Boy Advance is capable of a serious RPG.

* LAN PVP mode via GBA Game Link Cable</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun 2 - The Lost Age (U)(Megaroms).zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: The Lost Age</name>
		<desc>The story of Golden Sun: The Lost Age picks up right near the end of the first game. Golden Sun veterans will be surprised to learn that The Lost Age is played from the point of view of the party being chased as they try to light the remaining two lighthouses, which will unlock the power of alchemy for the world--or will it instead unlock the world's destruction?

* LAN PVP mode via GBA Game Link Cable</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun 2 - The Lost Age (U)(Megaroms)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyakuten Saiban (J)(Lightforce).zip</path>
		<name>Gyakuten Saiban</name>
		<desc>Not everyone is innocent until proven guilty! Players star as a defense attorney, who must prove his seemingly guilty client's innocence no matter how dire the circumstances may seem. The game presents twisting storylines and intriguing gameplay in a comical anime style. Players must collect evidence, weed through inconsistent testimonies, and overcome corrupt agendas to ensure that justice prevails.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gyakuten Saiban (J)(Lightforce)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyakuten Saiban 2 (J)(HP).zip</path>
		<name>Gyakuten Saiban 2</name>
		<desc>The second game in the popular court room battle series from Japan introduces four new cases featuring new characters, plot twists and gameplay features. Players resume the role of Phoenix Wright, a defence attorney who must prove his client's innocence against the toughest of odds and most ruthless of adversaries. Players must exercise their legal prowess as they collect evidence, examine witnesses, analyse testimonies and seek the truth to ensure that justice prevails.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gyakuten Saiban 2 (J)(HP)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyakuten Saiban 3 (J)(Suxxors).zip</path>
		<name>Gyakuten Saiban 3</name>
		<desc>Phoenix Wright is back as the third game in the popular Ace Attorney hand-held franchise. As Phoenix Wright, you'll play through five shocking new cases in first-person perspective. The game features two unique modes of play. In Investigations Mode you'll survey crime scenes, interview witnesses and gather evidence. You'll then present findings, listen to testimonials and examine witnesses in Court Mode. Trials AND Tribulations also includes the "Psyche-Lock" feature that allows Phoenix to use a line of questioning to reveal inconsistencies in witness testimony.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gyakuten Saiban 3 (J)(Suxxors)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts: Chain of Memories</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in Castle Oblivion, a mysterious castle kept by Marluxia. Sora and his teammates are told that the castle causes visitors to lose their memories upon entering. The lobby and areas between floors are white with flower-themed decorations, but each floor can be transformed into a different world from the first Kingdom Hearts game using "world cards" created from Sora's memories. Like before, many of the worlds are based on Disney films while the rest were created by Square Enix.

Unlike the previous game, the worlds are created from Sora's memories. As such, many of the events experienced in Kingdom Hearts are relived in this game; Sora encounters memory-based versions of Disney characters that he has met before. The individual plotlines differ from those in the original game and revolve around the theme of memory. The exception is the Deep Jungle world which does not reappear in Chain of Memories. Just as Kingdom Hearts had several worlds created specifically for that game, Chain of Memories introduces Twilight Town, in addition to the original worlds of Kingdom Hearts. The world card for Twilight Town was created from memories on "the other side of Sora's heart".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories (U)(Venom)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20041111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia - The Ruins Of Lore (U)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Lufia: The Ruins of Lore</name>
		<desc>This exciting new chapter in the Lufia saga follows the adventures of Eldin, Torma, and Rami, a group of friends and would-be hunters as they set out in search of treasure, only to discover that fate has much more in store for them! Will they be able to solve the mysteries of the ancient ruins and stop the power-hungry leader Ragule from resurrecting the ancient beast, or will Ragules ambitions be realized at the expense of mankind? Prepare for the Adventure of a Lifetime!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Lufia - The Ruins Of Lore (U)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atelier Double</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar Legend (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Lunar Legend</name>
		<desc>You play Alex, a young boy who hopes to one day be a Dragonmaster like his dearly departed hero Dyne. One day, a wizard named Nash comes into town, and needs an escort to a nearby shrine in the woods. You, your childhood friend Luna, and your flying cat-like pet Nall accompany Nash to the shrine, and your adventure begins.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Lunar Legend (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Rings</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Vacation (J)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Magical Vacation</name>
		<desc>Once upon a time, war erupted for three days in the magic kingdom Kovomaka. This war was kept a secret from ordinary citizens, but one man began to travel all around the country in preparation for the next battle, and several years later, the game's main character enters the magic school Will-O-Wisp at the invitation of the school's principal. The main character possessed the ability to see and interact with spirits since youth, and was ostracized because of this ability.

The students of the Will-O-Wisp school are sent away to a summer school by the Valencia seaside despite warnings that several students from other schools had gone missing on the beach in the past. One afternoon, a strange monster called an Enigma appears on the beach, abducting some of the students. The hero must find the missing students and uncover the mysteries of the Enigma and war that occurred in the kingdom.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Magical Vacation (J)(Eurasia)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20011207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marie, Elie &amp; Anis No Atelier - Soyokaze Kara No Dengon (J)(Polla).zip</path>
		<name>Marie, Elie &amp; Anis no Atelier: Soyokaze kara no Dengon</name>
		<desc>Marie, Elie &amp; Anis no Atelier: Soyokaze kara no Dengon is a Strategy game, published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 2003.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Marie, Elie &amp; Anis No Atelier - Soyokaze Kara No Dengon (J)(Polla)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030124T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Battle Chip Challenge (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man: Battle Chip Challenge</name>
		<desc>Battle-focused installment in the Mega Man (Rockman) franchise. Bring it On... Rise to the Challenge! Face off against your opponents, 4arn new battle cards and chips and power 'em up, and test your skills in cool new battle scenes and prepare for the ultimate battle for "Net Domination" in the Battle Chip Grand Prix. Choose familiar characters from the Battle Network universe—including Mega Man and Guts Man, meet an all new Net-Navi character, and render shots, sword maneuvers and specialized moves with your Battle Chips. Released in Japan as Rockman EXE Battle Chip GP, Mega Man Battle Chip Challenge supports combat for two players via link-up.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Battle Chip Challenge (U)(Venom)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>DreamCatcher Interactive Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network</name>
		<desc>In the future, a young net-battler named Lan, boots his 'personal exploration terminal' (PET) and prepares to hack into the network to battle net crime. Lan's PET is no ordinary network navigator. It's Mega Man.EXE, the cyber-identity, which infiltrates the crime-ridden network to battle destructive computer viruses. Defeat viruses in real time and collect Battle Chips program data, containing valuable weapons data and critical system info. Collect over 175 Battle Chips to help Land and Mega Man.EXE restore peace and order to the network.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network (U)(Venom)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 2 (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network</name>
		<desc>In the future, a young net-battler named Lan, boots his 'personal exploration terminal' (PET) and prepares to hack into the network to battle net crime. Lan's PET is no ordinary network navigator. It's Mega Man.EXE, the cyber-identity, which infiltrates the crime-ridden network to battle destructive computer viruses. Defeat viruses in real time and collect Battle Chips program data, containing valuable weapons data and critical system info. Collect over 175 Battle Chips to help Land and Mega Man.EXE restore peace and order to the network.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 2 (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 3 Blue Version (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 3: Blue Version</name>
		<desc>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from cyber mayhem in the most expansive battle network adventure yet. Together with the White version, find all of Mega Man's battle style changes, "Giga Class" Chips, enemies and discover more surprises just for you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 3 Blue Version (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 3 White Version (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 3: White Version</name>
		<desc>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from viruses and cyber menaces. You'll travel through new virtual and real worlds, fight-off new bosses, interact with new characters and even find new Battle Chips. It's cyber mayhem at it's best!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 3 White Version (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 4 Blue Moon (U)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 4: Blue Moon</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment in the Mega Man Battle Network series comes in two versions--Red Sun and Blue Moon--each with different enemies, battle chips, souls, and characters. Once again, you assume the role of Lan as he and his friend, Mega Man.exe, fight to rid the Internet of viruses and other cyberworld enemies. Unlike previous games in the series, Mega Man Battle Network 4 focuses on a tournament system where players encounter a variety of enemies that must be defeated. A new Soul Unison system lets Mega Man transform into his defeated enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 4 Blue Moon (U)(Rising Sun)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 4 Red Sun (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 4: Red Sun</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment in the Mega Man Battle Network series comes in two versions--Red Sun and Blue Moon--each with different enemies, battle chips, souls, and characters. Once again, you assume the role of Lan as he and his friend, Mega Man.exe, fight to rid the Internet of viruses and other cyberworld enemies. Unlike previous games in the series, Mega Man Battle Network 4 focuses on a tournament system where players encounter a variety of enemies that must be defeated. A new Soul Unison system lets Mega Man transform into his defeated enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 4 Red Sun (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Battle Network 5 - Team Colonel (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Colonel</name>
		<desc>Team Colonel is the second edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Battle Network 5 - Team Colonel (U)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Battle Network 5 - Team Protoman (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Protoman</name>
		<desc>Team Protoman is the first edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Battle Network 5 - Team Protoman (U)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Falzar (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 6: Cybeast Falzar</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Falzar (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Gregar (U)(LightForce).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 6: Cybeast Gregar</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Gregar (U)(LightForce)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Zero (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero</name>
		<desc>It's your mission to help the exiled scientist Ciel discover the source of a new reploid energy! Play as Mega Man's pal Zero, the reploid from the Mega Man X series turned good by the infectious Sigma Virus and 100 years of sleep. Conquer your adversaries and find the energy source... or risk ultimate defeat. It's up to you to defend good from the destructive powers in the universe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Zero (U)(Venom)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20020910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Zero 2 (U)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 2</name>
		<desc>In Zero's next mission, he falls prey to a trap set by Neo Arcadia's ruthless commander. Planning to trick Zero, he tries to use him to wreak chaos between reploids and humans once again. But, can he succeed?

LAN Multiplayer

If you have two cartridges and a link cable, the players can link two GBAs and take part in a two-player game. There are three modes available to take part in:

- Time Attack - Set a goal somewhere in the stage. After three tries, the player with the shortest time to the goal wins.
- Enemy Battle - Defeat the most enemies from the generator within the time limit.
- Get Item - Collect the most items from the map within the time limit.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Zero 2 (U)(Eurasia)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20031014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Zero 3 (U)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 3</name>
		<desc>It's the third chapter in the Mega Man Zero action adventure series for the Game Boy Advance. Featuring a new customization system, you can now equip Zero, with a combination of chips that will affect both his attributes and abilities, allowing you to adapt him to different challenges. Among his other new skills, Zero will now have weapon called the recoil rod. Now be jumps at double his normal height. These new skills will allow our hero to march into Arcadia to defeat the evil Omega single-handedly ... Or will they?

GBA Game Link Cable</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Zero 3 (U)(Rising Sun)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20041005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Zero 4 (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 4</name>
		<desc>The Zero Knuckle... the baddest new tool in Zero's arsenal lets you steal enemies' weapons and use them in battle. Employ this along with countless other cool moves to fight the Neo Arcadian army, defeat the evil Dr. Weil and help the caravan of humans reach the peace and security of Area Zero.

GBA Game Link Cable</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MegaMan Zero 4 (U)(Trashman)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Max 2 Kai (J)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Max 2 Kai</name>
		<desc>Metal Max 2 Kai is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Now Production, which was released in Japan in 2003.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metal Max 2 Kai (J)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030620T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Now Production Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Fusion (U)(GBANow).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid Fusion</name>
		<desc>Samus Aran returns in an all-new Metroid adventure!

While lending mission support on planet SR388, interstellar bounty hunter Samus Aran is attacked by an X parasite, an organism with the ability to mimic the abilities of any creature it infects. Near death, Samus is saved by a vaccine made from the DNA of the last Metroid -- the X parasite's only natural predator. When the X spread to a research station in orbit around SR388, a weakened Samus is forced to exterminate them all ... or die trying.

The bonus features in Prime can be unlocked by linking between the game and Fusion via the Nintendo GameCube – Game Boy Advance link cable.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Fusion (U)(GBANow)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20021117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Zero Mission (U)(TrashMan).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid: Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>The full story of Samus Aran's first mission finally unfolds...

The first Metroid game just scratched the surface of the cataclysmic events on planet Zebes, and at long last the rest of the tale has come to light. Experience the first of Samus's legendary adventures through all-new cut-scenes and action sequences as the bounty hunter races through the deeps toward her showdown with the leader of the Space Pirates. But will the end of Mother Brain really mean the end of the story...?

Completion of the game unlocks an emulated version of the original Metroid game. Zero Mission also allow players to unlock the Metroid Fusion picture gallery by linking between Zero Mission and Fusion cartridges via the Game Boy Advance Game Link Cable.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Zero Mission (U)(TrashMan)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Advance (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Advance</name>
		<desc>Monster Rancher Advance is a Strategy Role-Playing game, developed and published by Tecmo, which was released in 2001.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monster Rancher Advance (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Advance 2 (U)(Venom).zip</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Advance 2</name>
		<desc>Monster Rancher Advance 2 lets players create, train, and fight with monsters of their own choosing. Monsters are generated by inputting key phrases to create different monsters. Each phrase entered will create a unique monster, which will always appear when that specific phrase is entered. Players can experiment with many different phrases for unexpected results. Two separate monsters can also be combined with special items to form an entirely new monster. Certain combinations will lead to hidden, rare monsters which can not be obtained through the normal monster generation process.

The Coaching System from Monster Rancher Advance has been dramatically improved for added depth in the sequel. Depending on the monster type, certain coaches will offer unique training sessions which other monster coaches will not be able to provide. These special training sessions can be very difficult and dangerous, yet have potential to yield major results. A monster's charisma and skills will also be crucial factors in deciding whether it is suitable to be a good coach or not. Coaches will now recognize and alert you to certain warnings which your breeding assistant may not notice.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monster Rancher Advance 2 (U)(Venom)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mother 1+2 (J)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Mother 1+2</name>
		<desc>Mother tells the story of Ninten, a 12-year-old boy who journeys around the world using his psychic powers to collect eight melodies in order to save the planet from an evil race of mind-controlling aliens. Mother 2 tells the story of Ness, a young boy who journeys around the world also using psychic powers to collect eight melodies in order to save the future from an alien of pure evil, intending to sentence all of reality to the horror of eternal darkness.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mother 1+2 (J)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030620T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pax Softnica</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mother 3 (J)(WRG).zip</path>
		<name>Mother 3</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the World of Mother 3.

The Nowhere Islands are an idyllic place; the residents of Tazmily Village live peacefully and in harmony with nature and with each other. But this all changes when the mysterious Pigmask Army arrives and proceeds to destroy and corrupt, with force and sly persuasion alike. Lucas and his friends must find out who wants to destroy the tranquility of Nowhere Islands and turn them into a high-tech nightmare.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mother 3 (J)(WRG)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brownie Brown, HAL Laboratory, Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Natural 2 Duo (J)(KaMX).zip</path>
		<name>Natural 2: Duo</name>
		<desc>Natural 2: Duo is an Adventure game, published by Omega Micott, which was released in Japan in 2002.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Natural 2 Duo (J)(KaMX)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020628T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Omega Micott Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oriental Blue - Ao no Tengai (J)(Cezar).zip</path>
		<name>Oriental Blue: Ao no Tengai</name>
		<desc>Oriental Blue: Ao No Tengai is an RPG from the Far East of Eden series. It has a unique magic system and different pathways the story can take depending on in-game choices.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Oriental Blue - Ao no Tengai (J)(Cezar)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pia Carrot e Youkoso!! 3.3 (J)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<name>Pia Carrot e Youkoso!! 3.3</name>
		<desc>Handheld spin-off from Pia Carrot 3.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pia Carrot e Youkoso!! 3.3 (J)(Rising Sun)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>F&amp;C</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Interchannel, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Emerald (U)(TrashMan).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Emerald Kaizo</name>
		<desc>This is a significantly more challenging hack of Pokémon Emerald, where the player can obtain all 386 Pokémon in the Third Generation.

Certain areas have been redesigned, to keep with the Kaizo theme. Keep a particular eye out on changing bike types. Once you cross an area obstacle with a certain bike type, it is very likely that there will be another that requires the other bike, and vice versa.

Most of the changes are trainer battles, and trainer placements. Sets are all changed, and there are many avoidable overworld double battles, but some may be unavoidable. Gyms follow specific themes, and have different trainers than the original. The Victory Road will be the toughest Victory Road of all the Kaizo Hacks.

Pokémon Battles do not allow the use of any item, except for held items. This is where the difficulty of the game comes from, so make sure you heal yourself before any battle, or else you cannot heal.

There are some small liberties taken in regards to certain story elements, one will fight more encounters with Team Magma and Team Aqua for instance. Magma Admin Courtney, not found in the original, can be fought in this version, for example.

Postgame is heavily changed up. You fight gym leader rematches at their full power, right off the bat. Starting with singles, then moving on to doubles.

To get Rayquaza, the player has to complete Trick House, which involves going through various Kaizo Challenges. However, it opens up only after the Champion is defeated.

There are areas in the game that can only be accessed once one beat the game, which can house a Legendary Pokémon, or some Pokémon that you can only get once you beat the game. This includes event items, so be sure to check for obscure areas in the game, because that is where those items are located. Then you can head to Lilycove and travel to the mysterious destinations.

The game is extremely challenging, but very fun, as the level curves are still steady, and you will be tested by various boss fights. Certain areas in the game are going to be incredibly brutal, and some will be rather grueling. This is not a hack for the faint of heart. It is much more difficult than every third gen hard mode hack.


Level Curve

Rival: 5
Roxanne: 14-15
Optional Rival: 14-16
Brawly: 16-17
Rival: 19-21
Wattson: 27-28
Tabitha: 36-37
Maxie: 38-39
Flannery: 41-42
Norman: 45
Shelly: 49
Rival: 50
Winona: 54-55
Aqua Admin Matt: 56
Last Rival Battle: 59-60
Magma Admin: 64-65
Maxie: 66
Matt: 67
Tate and Liza: 70
Magma Admin: 70
Maxie: 70-72
Shelly: 73
Archie: 75
Final Gym Leader: 76-77
Victory Road Average range: 75-78
Pokemon League: 100
Postgame Bosses: 100</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Emerald (U)(TrashMan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20170619T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing, Strategy, Unofficial</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Fire Red (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Pokemon Fire Red: Rocket Edition</name>
		<desc>If ya can't beat 'em, join 'em! Join the nefarious Team Rocket and steal Pokemon, extort people, and stay one step ahead of the law. This game features the ability to steal Pokemon from the trainers you beat. Rise through the ranks of Team Rocket, and uncover secret plots to gain control of the Kanto region!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Fire Red (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20200513T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Unofficial</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Ruby (U)(Mugs).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Ruby Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Ruby. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Ruby (U)(Mugs)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Sapphire (U)(Mugs).zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Sapphire Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Sapphire. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Sapphire is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Sapphire (U)(Mugs)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rebelstar - Tactical Commmand (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Rebelstar: Tactical Command</name>
		<desc>You can play as the leader of a revolt in the turn-based strategy game Rebelstar: Tactical Command. The Arelian Empire seized control of Earth 70 years ago and has since become an oppressive regime, controlling the world with fear and marauding shock troops. You can fight back by equipping a team of rebels and controlling them in battle. Rebelstar: Tactical Command includes campaign, skirmish, multiplayer hotseat, and multiplayer link mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Rebelstar - Tactical Commmand (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codo Games</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Riviera - The Promised Land (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Riviera: The Promised Land</name>
		<desc>In Riviera: The Promised Land, you'll follow two fierce warriors--each armed with godly weapons--in a mission to defeat demons once and for all. The adventure included lets you experience more than 30 hours of role-playing gameplay, complete with minigames, multiple endings, and secret paths and items. The game's unique item system allows items to function differently depending on which characters equip them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Riviera - The Promised Land (U)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SD Gundam G Generation Advance (J)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>SD Gundam G Generation Advance</name>
		<desc>Another title in the SD Gundam G Generation franchise. This game follows the system of the Wonderswan G-Gen games, and features a crossover plot.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/SD Gundam G Generation Advance (J)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vanguard Games</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shingata Medarot - Kabuto Version (J)(Caravan).zip</path>
		<name>Shingata Medarot: Kabuto Version</name>
		<desc>Shingata Medarot is a remake of the first Medarot and was the last game in the series until its DS entry years later. Its art style is a huge departure from its predecessors'.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Shingata Medarot - Kabuto Version (J)(Caravan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20041216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shining Force - Resurrection of the Dark Dragon (U)(TrashMan).zip</path>
		<name>Shining Force: Resurrection of the Dark Dragon</name>
		<desc>Shining Force is a turn-based tactical RPG. Battles take place in square grids, and each unit occupies one square. Each unit can move up to a fixed amount of squares along the battlefield, determined by its Move statistic. Depending on its location relative to enemies and to allies, a unit can also perform one action: attack, cast a spell, use an item, or search the area. Some commands, such as equipping or dropping items, don't count as actions. The order of turns is determined by the unit's agility score and a random seed.

As is most common for the RPG genre, units become stronger by fighting enemies or by performing other actions in battle, such as healing allies. These actions give the units experience points (EXP.), which allow them to gain levels.

In Shining Force, each allied unit is represented by a character with his or her own background and personality, much like in the Fire Emblem series. Although there are no "generic" units, except on the enemy side, most characters contribute little or nothing to the plot upon joining the player army.

Each allied unit also has a class, which defines a set of abilities for that unit and determines the spells and equipment they have access to. A unit can be promoted to another class at any level between 10 or 20. Upon promotion the character's level resets to 1 and statistics are reduced by a fixed amount, although they begin higher if the character had been promoted at a higher level.

Battle goals for the player are fairly simple: kill all enemies, kill the enemies' leader, or advance to a town or landmark. The enemy side wins if they kill the player's leader, Max, or if the player chooses to escape the battle by casting Egress. Even if the player army is defeated, the player can recover allies and retry the battle. The Force keeps any experience that is obtained, regardless of the battle's outcome. Thus, there is no Game Over, and the player's army gets stronger even upon its defeat, although Max's death results in the player losing half of their money.

Most games in the Shining Force series (with the exceptions of Shining Force CD, all three Game Gear games, all five cell phone games, the Shining Force III premium disc, the Shining Force for Palm Pilot game, and Shining Force Feather) also possess an exploration mode that occurs outside of battle. This gameplay mode is essentially a Japanese-style traditional RPG game, along the lines of Final Fantasy or Dragon Quest, although there are no labyrinths and few puzzles to solve. In this mode, the player's army is represented by Max, who is able to walk around, interact with people, find treasure, buy equipment and items, outfit the army, and choose which of the army's members will be used in battle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Shining Force - Resurrection of the Dark Dragon (U)(TrashMan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shining Soul (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Shining Soul</name>
		<desc>Enter a world of magic and mystery, where your closest allies may sometimes turn out to be your worst enemies. Shining Soul puts you in the middle of a desperate struggle between the Dark Dragon and a group of warriors known as the Shining Fleet. In the final stage of the war, you can play one of four character classes: fighter, wizard, archer, or dragonute. Customize your character's color schemes, weapons, and armor, and then explore the world of Shining Soul either alone or with three of your friends.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Shining Soul (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shining Soul II (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Shining Soul II</name>
		<desc>As monsters begin to appear in the kingdom Klantol, King Marcel announces a grand tournament at the coliseum to find a hero that can protect the country. Now, as a mighty Brawler, Priestess, Dark Wizard, or Ninja, you must accept the king's challenge. Each character has certain strengths and weaknesses that can mean the difference between victory and defeat in single-player, multiplayer, or cooperative multiplayer modes. In addition to valuable weapons and armor, you can equip your party with Force Links, which, when combined, create a Shining Force--a powerful weapon capable of decimating the enemy forces.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Shining Soul II (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sigma Star Saga (U)(Trashman).zip</path>
		<name>Sigma Star Saga</name>
		<desc>When a double-agent's allegiance begins to waver, the galaxy finds itself in a precarious position.

Humanity is struggling to survive against the Krill onslaught. Ian Recker, a decorated pilot, goes undercover to investigate the Krill's secrets, but finds himself trapped in a moral dilemma.

The first RPG on Game Boy Advance to combine a deep storyline and well-developed characters with a space-shooter battle engine.

Customizable weapons including over 15,000 Gun Data combinations.

Branching storyline with four ending and 20+ hours of gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sigma Star Saga (U)(Trashman)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sister Princess Re Pure (J)(Polla).zip</path>
		<name>Sister Princess: Re Pure</name>
		<desc>Sister Princess: Re Pure is an Adventure game, developed and published by Marvelous Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 2003.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sister Princess Re Pure (J)(Polla)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summon Night - Swordcraft Story (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story</name>
		<desc>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is an action role-playing game by Banpresto for the Nintendo Game Boy Advance system. It is part of the Summon Night series of games. Atlus handled the English translation of the game. It has a sequel, Summon Night: Swordcraft Story 2.

Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is set in the strange world of Lyndbaum, a sacred land linked to four magical dimensions from which Summoners can call forth spirits called Guardian Beasts to do their bidding.

Summon Night: Swordcraft Story progresses through the story on a day-by-day basis. The entire game consists of 10 days, where the player traverses through the town of Wystern and the Labyrinth Dungeon. Each day, more levels of the Labyrinth are unlocked and the player is required to travel deeper to complete mandatory quests. A day normally ends after a tournament or boss battle. During the night, the player can choose who to spend the night with, which will control the following cutscene.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Summon Night - Swordcraft Story (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flight-Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summon Night - Swordcraft Story 2 (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story</name>
		<desc>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is an action role-playing game by Banpresto for the Nintendo Game Boy Advance system. It is part of the Summon Night series of games. Atlus handled the English translation of the game. It has a sequel, Summon Night: Swordcraft Story 2.

Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is set in the strange world of Lyndbaum, a sacred land linked to four magical dimensions from which Summoners can call forth spirits called Guardian Beasts to do their bidding.

Summon Night: Swordcraft Story progresses through the story on a day-by-day basis. The entire game consists of 10 days, where the player traverses through the town of Wystern and the Labyrinth Dungeon. Each day, more levels of the Labyrinth are unlocked and the player is required to travel deeper to complete mandatory quests. A day normally ends after a tournament or boss battle. During the night, the player can choose who to spend the night with, which will control the following cutscene.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Summon Night - Swordcraft Story 2 (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flight-Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summon Night Craft Sword Monogatari - Hajimari no Ishi (J)(Caravan).zip</path>
		<name>Summon Night Craft Sword Monogatari: Hajimari no Ishi</name>
		<desc>Summon Night Craft Sword Monogatari: Hajimari no Ishi is a Role-Playing game, developed by Flight-Plan and published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 2005.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Summon Night Craft Sword Monogatari - Hajimari no Ishi (J)(Caravan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flight-Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ghouls N Ghosts (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls 'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>As dauntless knight Arthur you are caught up in the most dangerous of quests! A spell has been cast upon the kingdom. Your fair maiden, Princess Prin Prin has been snatched up by the evil emperor. Only as Arthur can you get her back from the creatures of the undead that haunt the land. Test your courage and skill to the limit. You must keep up the quest. On your journey, your mightiest weapon of all awaits you... MAGIC!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Ghouls N Ghosts (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020923T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation (U)(Jam Project).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation</name>
		<desc>It is two hundred years after the beginning of the "Space Era", a time period when civilization began expanding into space. However, by the start of the 21st century, two meteors struck and destroyed much of the Earth, sending humanity into chaos. By year 179 of the Space Era, secret technology, dubbed Extra-Over Technology, or EOT, was discovered by the Earth Federal Government within a third meteor that had hit Earth at the Marquesas Islands in the South Pacific. Dr. Bian Zoldark, while investigating the meteor, also found out that the creators of the Extra-Over Technology were heading to Earth to reclaim it. In order to defend earth, the government starts to develop a group of humanoid mecha, known as Personal Troopers.
The alien race that created Extra-Over Technology, called the Aerogaters by the Earth Federal Government, initially attacks an Earth ship sent out to investigate their presence in the far reaches of the solar system. This initial skirmish ends in a defeat for the Aerogaters, prompting them to sue for negotiations with the Earth Federation Army. Talks are arranged to take place at a secret facility in Antarctica, but the talks are targeted by a rogue faction called the Divine Crusaders.
The Divine Crusaders destroys the Aerogater delegation, then turn on the Federation forces. Bian Zoldark, revealing himself to be the leader of the Divine Crusaders, announces the existence of the Aerogaters to the world and rebel against the Earth Government. As Earth spins into civil war, a new Aerogater force is on the move, seeking to reclaim their lost technology...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation (U)(Jam Project)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation 2 (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation</name>
		<desc>It is two hundred years after the beginning of the "Space Era", a time period when civilization began expanding into space. However, by the start of the 21st century, two meteors struck and destroyed much of the Earth, sending humanity into chaos. By year 179 of the Space Era, secret technology, dubbed Extra-Over Technology, or EOT, was discovered by the Earth Federal Government within a third meteor that had hit Earth at the Marquesas Islands in the South Pacific. Dr. Bian Zoldark, while investigating the meteor, also found out that the creators of the Extra-Over Technology were heading to Earth to reclaim it. In order to defend earth, the government starts to develop a group of humanoid mecha, known as Personal Troopers.
The alien race that created Extra-Over Technology, called the Aerogaters by the Earth Federal Government, initially attacks an Earth ship sent out to investigate their presence in the far reaches of the solar system. This initial skirmish ends in a defeat for the Aerogaters, prompting them to sue for negotiations with the Earth Federation Army. Talks are arranged to take place at a secret facility in Antarctica, but the talks are targeted by a rogue faction called the Divine Crusaders.
The Divine Crusaders destroys the Aerogater delegation, then turn on the Federation forces. Bian Zoldark, revealing himself to be the leader of the Divine Crusaders, announces the existence of the Aerogaters to the world and rebel against the Earth Government. As Earth spins into civil war, a new Aerogater force is on the move, seeking to reclaim their lost technology...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation 2 (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen A (J)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen A</name>
		<desc>Super Robot Wars A (Advance) is the first Super Robot Wars on the Game Boy Advance. The Londo Bell forces battle against the Shadow Mirror.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen A (J)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010921T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AI</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen D (J)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen D</name>
		<desc>The 4th Super Robot Wars on the Game Boy Advance, D (Destiny) chronicles the battle against the Ruina.

Super Robot Wars D is the fourth Super Robot Wars game for the GBA. Unlike its (traditional) predecessor, Super Robot Wars R, D offers a more diverse selection of anime series, getting rid of mainstays like G Gundam, Gundam 0083, Zambot 3/Daitarn 3 and Combattler V/Voltes V for debuting series like Daltanius, The Big O and Megazone 23.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen D (J)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AI</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen J (J)(WRG).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen J</name>
		<desc>The last installment of the Super Robot Wars series for the Game Boy Advance. Notable for its battle animations, which are arguably on the level of the Playstation 2 versions of the series.

This game is notable for being the only anime-based SRW to not feature the Getter Robo franchise, the first of only two anime-based games to not feature series from Gundam's Universal Century timelime, and the first to include a battle-armor series (which technically isn't robot anime).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen J (J)(WRG)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A.I Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen R (J)(Eurasia).zip</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen R</name>
		<desc>The second Super Robot Wars game for the Game Boy Advance, R (Reversal) follows the battles of the "Round Knights" as they fight against various mecha anime villains.

Super Robot Wars R is the second Super Robot Wars game for the Game Boy Advance. The game adds no new mechanics to the franchise, and is identical to its predecessor in many ways, including the usage of "static" sprites, much of the anime roster, and general interface. The game does, however, implement many of the changes introduced in Super Robot Wars Alpha and Alpha Gaiden that were not present in Super Robot Wars A.

R removes the original Gundam series, Gundam 0083, Daimos, the classic Getter Robo series and Dragonar, and replaces them with Gundam X and the debuting Gear Fighter Dendoh, Shin vs. Neo Getter Robo, and Nadesico: Prince of Darkness.

The story follows the Excellence Team, including main character Raul or Fiona Gureden (depending on the player's choice), as they find themselves caught in the middle of the events of Nadesico: Prince of Darkness or Mobile Suit Gundam: Char's Counterattack. After an ambush by a mysterious entity, the Excellence Team is thrown into the past.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen R (J)(Eurasia)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020802T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AI</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of Mana (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Sword of Mana</name>
		<desc>The Mana Tree Needs Defenders!

The location of the Mana Tree - wellspring of all life - has long been lost to legend. Many centuries have passed, and the Granz Realm's Dark Lord is searching for the secrets of the ancient tree so that he can control the source of Mana. Now, a young hero and heroine must come together to defeat the evil that threatens both the mystical tree and the world itself.

Choose your hero! Guide a battle-hardened gladiator on his quest to avenge the deaths of his parents!

...Or guide a young girl, one of the last survivors of the Mana Clan, as she confronts the past that haunts her.

Experience the saga of these two heroes as their stories weave together and they join forces to protect the Mana Tree from the powers of darkness.

Unlike prior games in the series, Sword of Mana does not have a direct multiplayer component. Instead, players can connect their Game Boy Advances together via a Link Cable to give their characters powerful attacks to be used at a later time, known as the "Amigo" system. The original game featured no multiplayer capabilities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sword of Mana (U)(Mode7)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20030829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tactics Ogre - The Knight of Lodis (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Tactics Ogre: The Knight of Lodis</name>
		<desc>Tactics Ogre: The Knight of Lodis is a tactical role-playing game developed by Quest. It was released by Nintendo in Japan in 2001 on the Game Boy Advance, then later released by Atlus in North America in 2002.

Like Tactics Ogre: Let Us Cling Together, The Knight of Lodis features party-based tactical combat on an isometric playing field. The player has limited control outside of battle, being provided only extremely limited movement on a world map, a shop function, an options menu, and an option to participate in a training session in which the player pits its own forces against each other in order to gain experience. Characters can be hired or acquired in combat, and there are interchangeable classes and a wide array of weapons, equipment and magic spells.

Under the watchful eye of the Holy Lodis Empire, strange things are happening on the island of Ovis. Powerful forces have been set in motion, but their motives are masked by political intrigue. It is your mission to investigate these occurrences and discover the true intentions of those involved. The ending of the game will depend on the actions that the main character, Alphonse, takes. You will make many revelations as you proceed, but you must survive the unrelenting battles and cultivate your characters' abilities to unveil the ultimate truth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tactics Ogre - The Knight of Lodis (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020511T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Phantasia (U)(Independent).zip</path>
		<name>Tales of Phantasia</name>
		<desc>For young swordsman Cress Albane, it wasn't a typical day out hunting in the nearby woods. He had no hint of the tragedy unfolding back home. Battle in real time: The Linear Motion Battle System puts the emphasis on action as you attack your enemies without the use of menus. New game events, dialogue sequences, and other features enhance the adventure. Crack open the Monster Dictionary to view the strengths and weaknesses of the enemies you've met in battle. Players will want to collect data on them all. Use the innovative Cooking System to collect ingredients and recipes to brew up meals that restore your health and magic.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tales of Phantasia (U)(Independent)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of the World - Summoner's Lineage (J)(Cezar).zip</path>
		<name>Tales of the World: Summoner's Lineage</name>
		<desc>A spin-off of the Tales series set in the Tales of Phantasia universe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tales of the World - Summoner's Lineage (J)(Cezar)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magical Company</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wizardry Summoner (J)(Lord Moyne).zip</path>
		<name>Wizardry Summoner</name>
		<desc>Wizardry Summoner is an Japanese only entry to the classic RPG series, released for the Game Boy Advance in 2001.

Like in most Wizardry games, you control a party (user created or using preset characters) and explore dungeons.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Wizardry Summoner (J)(Lord Moyne)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fupac</developer>
		<publisher>Media Rings Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yggdra Union - We will Never Fight Alone (U)(Rising Sun).zip</path>
		<name>Yggdra Union: We'll Never Fight Alone</name>
		<desc>The game is a tactical RPG with an overhead view of a 2D map, managing miniature versions of the units. A card system dictating unit movement and potential skills plays into both enemy and ally turns, as well as the "Union" formation system, in which massive battles can take place between several platoons. There are also some real time elements included during actual battle sequences, such as being able to control how units attack the enemy.

Ruled by a royal family said to be descendants of the gods themselves, Fantasinia is a prosperous and peaceful land -- until the peace is shattered by the invading forces of the Empire of Bronkia. Led by the young emperor Gulcasa, who seized control of the Empire in a brutal coup d'etat, Bronchia's Imperial Army cuts a bloody swath through the people of Fantasinia and the Royal Armies of King Ordeene. Amidst the chaos, a young woman escapes from the besieged capital of Partina -- a woman with innocence in her face, and a sword in her hand. The girl's name is Princess Yggdra, the last surviving member of the royal family; the sword is the Gran Centurio, a legendary blade once wielded by the founder of Fantasinia, and passed down through generations of royalty. Fleeing to to a remote valley at the southern tip of the continent, Yggdra meets up with Milanor, the charismatic leader of a band of thieves, and readies herself for a war of liberation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Yggdra Union - We will Never Fight Alone (U)(Rising Sun)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zone of the Enders - The Fist of Mars (U)(Mode7).zip</path>
		<name>Zone of the Enders: The Fist of Mars</name>
		<desc>Zone of the Enders: The Fist of Mars, known in Japan as Zone of the Enders: 2173 Testament, is a video game that was developed by Sunrise Interactive and published by Konami in 2001 for the Game Boy Advance. The game is story-orientated, and is based around turn-based strategic mecha combat.

The year is 2173 A.D. A young boy named Cage finds himself in control of a fully armed prototype mechanized robot and now he must prevent a space colony hijack of Mars. An army of trucks, tanks, fighters, and giant, anime-style robots all collide in this exciting new chapter of the Zone of the Enders saga.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Zone of the Enders - The Fist of Mars (U)(Mode7)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (U)(GBATemp).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The year is 2035 and Soma Cruz is about to witness the first solar eclipse of the 21st century when he suddenly blacks out -- only to awaken inside a mysterious castle. As Soma, you must navigate the castle's labyrinths while confronting perilous monsters at every turn. But beware, you must escape before the evil consumes you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (U)(GBATemp)-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210601T224554</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tsukihime (J).zip</path>
		<name>Tsukihime (J)</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210601T224627</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
